What happens in the kitchen ends up on the plate.
Waiting... is a comedy, romance film directed by Rob McKittrick.
Young employees at Shenaniganz restaurant collectively stave
off boredom and adulthood with their antics.
Monty, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Serena, played by Anna Faris.
Dean, played by Justin Long.
Dan, played by David Koechner.
Raddimus, played by Luis Guzmán.
Bishop, played by Chi McBride.
is a 2005 American comedy film starring Ryan Reynolds, Anna Faris, and
Justin Long as staffers at the restaurant Shenaniganz.
It is directed by Rob McKittrick in his directorial debut.
McKittrick wrote the screenplay while working as a waiter.
The script was initially sold in a film deal to Artisan Entertainment, but was
released by Lions Gate Entertainment (which purchased Artisan in 2003).
Producers Chris Moore and Jeff Balis of Live Planet's Project
Greenlight fame also took notice of the project and assisted.
The film made over US$6 million, more than twice the
budget of the film, in its opening weekend.
The film explores themes of decision, waiter, hostess,
trainee, employer employee relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.